[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these units for distance is the longest?", "correct_answer": "1 par sec", "incorrect_answers": ["1 light year", "1 galactic year", "1 astronomical unit"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What condition does the brother of Tom Cruises character suffer from in the 1988 Oscar-winning drama movie Rain Man?", "correct_answer": "Autism", "incorrect_answers": ["Obsessive\u2013compulsive disorder", "Schizophrenia", "Bipolar disorder"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Lance Henriksen stars in all the Alien movies.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The traffic lights has three colors. Yellow is in the middle.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A player begins a game of Magic: The Gathering with 40 life points.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which 1987 movie won the Best Picture Award?", "correct_answer": "The Last Emperor", "incorrect_answers": ["My Fair Lady", "On the Waterfront", "Gigi"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Luxembourg has a population of approximately how many people?", "correct_answer": "one half million", "incorrect_answers": ["30,000", "two million", "three and one half million"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "We learn from the film The Crow that Sarah likes her eggs done how?", "correct_answer": "Over easy", "incorrect_answers": ["Hard-boiled", "Scrambled", "Sunny side up"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which company built the A6M, aka Zero -- the fighter aircraft  that was used in the attack on Pearl Harbor?", "correct_answer": "Mitsubishi", "incorrect_answers": ["Toshiba", "Isuzu", "Mikayashi"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Blue is a British boy band consisting of four members. The song Signed, Sealed, Delivered, Im Yours is performed by them and this musician.", "correct_answer": "Stevie Wonder", "incorrect_answers": ["Jim Morrison", "Elton John", "Steve Lawrence"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What herb is known as Laotian coriander and Lao cilantro in Thailand and Vietnam?", "correct_answer": "Dill", "incorrect_answers": ["Marjoram", "Basil", "Jasmine"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is Chunks real name in the movie The Goonies?", "correct_answer": "Lawrence", "incorrect_answers": ["Bobby", "Clark", "Chuck"]}]